The tale of one of the most controversial video games of all time.
The Gamechangers is a drama, tv movie film directed by Owen Harris.
The struggle of Houser's legal feud against American lawyer Jack Thompson,
over the morality of the "Grand Theft Auto" video game series.
Sam Houser, played by Daniel Radcliffe.
Jack Thompson, played by Bill Paxton.
Jamie King, played by Joe Dempsie.
Jounalist, played by Ryan Gage.
Bridjet, played by Alex McGregor.
Doug Lowenstein, played by Nick Boraine.
The Gamechangers is a 2015 British docudrama produced by the BBC.
The programme is an unauthorised depiction of the controversies caused by Grand Theft Auto, a successful
video game series, as various attempts were made to halt the production of the games.
Directed by Owen Harris and written by James Wood, the film centres on the legal feud between Rockstar Games president Sam Houser (Daniel Radcliffe) and
Florida attorney Jack Thompson (Bill Paxton) over the video games and the debate regarding the psychological effects of violent video games.
The film explores themes of journalist, video
game, ghetto, biography, courtroom.
The tone is emotional.